the most important ingredient yes hard work is
there dedication is there passion is there but
I felt being honest is one of the
most important things be to start of being
honest to yourself unless you are honest to
yourself you can't be honest to others hi
ever met someone who speaks their mind honestly
without any filters that's called candor candor it's
about being open truthful and straightforward in what
you said imagine you're giving feedback to a
friend candor is when you are honest but
respectful sharing your thoughts without sugarcoating things it's
honesty at your best so the next time
when you're honest remember the word candor